

Saeed Molaei

React / Flutter Developer

Summary

https://github.com/saeed-molaei-dev

https://www.linkedin.com/in/Saeedmolaei-dev

Born in 1996 | Living in Mazandaran

saeedmolaei.dev@outlook.com

Hi, I'm a React / Flutter developer, with more than 1 year experience in fintech projects and now I'm looking for opportunity to grow my knowledge in React.

please visit my git for sample projects.

Experiences

Flutter Developer

Jan 2021 - Oct 2021

Babol

Daya Company

+98 936 948 64 68

Daya Tadbir Yousr company focuses on developing computer and mobile software for various applications including but not limited to banking, insurance, healthcare, telecommunication, and retail. The company also mainly focuses on (Artificial Intelligence) Al powered products.

- develop Iran Zamin Bank application from scratch, using provider and API's for develop pages like invoice, landing, transfer money and etc.
- develop DayaPay application from scratch
- Gained familiarity with Provider, API call

Self Learning

Jan 2019 - now planet earth

My PC

a pc that's help me to this journey

- learned HTML, CSS, JS, React
- learned Flutter, provider
- learned Adobe XD, Figma
- learned HTTP Clients like axios
- learned version controls

Skills

Tech

HTML, CSS SCSS JavaScript TypeScript React Redux Thunk

Flutter Tailwind Bootstrap

Collabration

Scrum Figma Adobe XD GIT

Exploaring

Vue

Courses

React advance course

2022-2022

keiykavoos zaman international co.

Education

Associate's degree in Software engineering

2013 - 2017

Imam Khomeini university of Behshahr (Mazandaran)

Languages

Persian English

Native pre-intermediate

Hobbies

Playing Games Watching Movies Learn New Things Taste New Foods Doing Exercises